I have now scheduled lectures about my
new book 12 rules for life and other
associated issues in 12 different cities
in the next three months the first talk
in New York takes place at the end of
March the remaining 11 occur in May
there will be more venues in the UK
Europe and Canada announced very soon
here are the cities and dates that have
already been booked New York Sunday
March 25th Toronto Thursday May 3rd
Washington Friday May 4th Chicago
Saturday May 5th
Detroit Sunday May 6th Denver Tuesday
May 8th San Francisco Wednesday May 9th
Seattle Thursday May 10th
London Sunday May 13th
Dallas Wednesday May 30th
Austin Thursday May 31st Phoenix Friday
June 1st tickets were on sale for my
patreon subscribers and viewers who have
signed up to my mailing list at Jordan B
Peterson calm until today except for New
York the first show tickets are
available to everyone for all cities as
of 10:00 a.m. local time today Friday
February 23rd for New York at the Beacon
Theatre tickets will be available to
everyone as of 11:00 a.m. local time
today Friday February 23rd thank you for
all your continued support I'm looking
forward to seeing you in the next few
months